[
  {
    "id": 0,
    "question": "சறுக்குமரம்",
    "answers": ["சறுக்குமரம்", "சறுக்கு"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "பந்து",
    "answers": ["பந்து", "கைப்பந்து"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "பட்டம்",
    "answers": ["பட்டம்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "ஏணிப்படி",
    "answers": ["ஏணிப்படி", "ஏணி"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "குச்சி",
    "answers": ["குச்சி", "கழி", "கம்பு", "கோல்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "மணல்",
    "answers": ["மணல்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "பாய்",
    "answers": ["பாய்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "தொப்பி",
    "answers": ["தொப்பி", "குல்லா"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "மிதவை",
    "answers": ["மிதவை"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "பலகை",
    "answers": ["பலகை", "மரப்பலகை"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "குற்றங்கடிதல்",
    "answers": ["குற்றங்கடிதல்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "ஏற்றத்தாழ்வு",
    "answers": ["ஏற்றத்தாழ்வு"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "தென்னம்பாளை",
    "answers": ["தென்னம்பாளை"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "தேரோட்டம்",
    "answers": ["தேரோட்டம்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "கழிவுநீர்",
    "answers": ["கழிவுநீர்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "எழுதுகோல்",
    "answers": ["எழுதுகோல்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "நன்னடத்தை",
    "answers": ["நன்னடத்தை"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "பொழுதுபோக்கு",
    "answers": ["பொழுதுபோக்கு"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "question": "தலையணை",
    "answers": ["தலையணை"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "வாரந்தோறும்",
    "answers": ["வாரந்தோறும்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "question": "இளவரசர்",
    "answers": ["இளவரசர்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  }
]
